[AI-generated narration] Backup success is not recovery success.
ProofRestore verifies recovery before an emergency.
I’ll open the demo vault.
The latest backup completed, but recoverability is at risk: eight snapshots hide two integrity issues and a retention risk.
I’ll check a file.
The request asks for my thesis from Tuesday evening.
Its history shows damaged recent versions and a verified Tuesday copy.
I’ll keep the interpreted time, choose the original location, and verify.
Deterministic code selects the eligible snapshot, finds the stored object, and proves its hash and size.
This version is fully recoverable.
The restore simulation changes nothing.
A newer destination file would conflict, so ProofRestore protects it instead of overwriting it.
These evidence entries trace the snapshot, path, object, matching hash and size, and conflict.
The downloaded proof report preserves the request, verdict, plan, methodology, and appendix.
Judges can test the same engine themselves.
The Recovery Lab reads selected files locally and changes only in-memory copies—nothing is uploaded or modified.
I’ll load the sample, corrupt one stored copy, and run the check.
The ordered log exposes every snapshot and byte change.
The fixed expected hash and changed observed hash produce hash mismatch and an unrecoverable result.
Judges can choose their own files or folder, remove an object, create a conflict, export the manifest, or continue through the full workflow.
Natural language interprets requests, but deterministic code decides recovery.
Backups should not require faith.